<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blockchain on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blockchain on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a safer crypto token</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190524-biweekly-report-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190524-biweekly-report-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles公链在过去两周(2019.05.11——05.24)期间的进展： * 5miles数据上链完成 * CMT Wallet 权益投票功能开发进展 * FairPlay</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles 主链成功升级，支持CMT Wallet 参与权益投票的接口</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190523-mainnet-upgrade-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190523-mainnet-upgrade-zh/</guid>
      <description>经过全体超级节点（验证人）的链上治理投票，CyberMiles公链于2019年5月23日成功地进行了无分叉的软件升级。本次升级至v0.1.8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The next wave in blockchain data</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190210-blockchaindate-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190210-blockchaindate-en/</guid>
      <description>Last year we provided an in-depth look into blockchain storage, also known as global state. In that article I compared the two vastly different types of data in an Ethereum-compatible blockchain: permanent data and ephemeral data.
Today let’s explore the use of the permanent data, more specifically how we currently can turn raw event log data into rich information, suitable for DApps. Allow me also to detail some design characteristics of off-chain data storage projects and, in turn, point out the enormous opportunities that are on the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Dr. Marc Fleury to CyberMiles!</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20180109-marc-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20180109-marc-en/</guid>
      <description>Twenty years ago, the Open Source community was at a crossroad. The method of decentralized software production (aka Open Source collaboration), championed by a small number of ideology-driven developers, had produced very impressive results such as the Linux operating system, the Apache web server, the GCC compilers, and much more. Yet, the mainstream software powerhouses were still skeptical and even hostile to software decentralization (Microsoft called it a “cancer”, worse than scam).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I accidentally killed it (and evaporated $300 million)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20171111-polkadotsafe-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20171111-polkadotsafe-en/</guid>
      <description>Github user devops199 said on Twitter “I accidentally killed it”. Before anyone can blink an eye, his “accident” has “killed” Ethereum accounts holding over $300M in crypto assets. On average, each of his 4 words cost $75M.
One of those Ethereum accounts belongs to the Polkadot project, and it held close to $90M before it was “killed”.
Someone asked devops199 after the incident: Why did you do it? His response?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CyberMiles?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20171015-cybermiles-overview-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20171015-cybermiles-overview-en/</guid>
      <description>What makes the CyberMiles blockchain and tokens so unique? Why do we call the CyberMiles Token (CMT) the “master token” for e-commerce? Join us through our token sale event!
 CyberMiles is a next generation blockchain for smart contracts. Its Smart Business Contract is designed to be far more powerful than Ethereum Smart Contracts. It will be the next generation Ethereum (ETH).  2.CyberMiles is optimized for e-commerce applications. It will provide a large library of commerce-related Smart Business Contracts, making it a breeze to build decentralized commerce applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>