<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:00:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More giveaways with FairPlay DApp are coming</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190703-faiplay-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190703-faiplay-en/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for all players who has participated the two-week giveaway and our lovely sponsors. We have 1900+ players in the last campaign in June.
FairPlay #DApp statistics round-up.
Amazing performance! Thanks go to all of our sponsors!!!
For more prizes, visit https://t.co/fvkD81v0rB@FairPlayDapp#luckydraw #fair #raffle #luck #win #prize #crypto #jackpot #blockchain #token #ecommerce #freebie #gift pic.twitter.com/Pp6DfUt9RF
&amp;mdash; CyberMiles (@cybermiles) June 27, 2019 
This campaign has ended with great popularity. For those who missed the chance to enter, no need to be regretful, because the giveaways are gonna keep coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to import your ERC-20 CMTs</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190627-import-erc-20-cmts-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190627-import-erc-20-cmts-en/</guid>
      <description>First, you’ll need to download the CyberMiles App to your device. Once downloaded, select “Import Wallet” at the bottom of your screen.
There are three (3) ways to import your ERC20 CMT: by mnemonic words, private key, or keystore. Choose one of these methods**.
**Note: During your import, be advised that you must remember your mnemonic words, private key, or keystore and password, and your imported CMT wallet’s password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles App Releases its Newest Version, Enabling Staking Function</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles App (formerly CMT Wallet)3.0 is officially launched, and the mobile App staking CMT function is now enabled! Now users can use the CyberMiles App to stake their CMTs to validators (supernodes) to get block revenue. Come and download here!
Based on the current stake of the whole network, now that the stake 10,000 CMT, the compensation rate is 30%, the block income that can be obtained in one year is 1515 CMTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMT 手机权益投票已经上线，快来获取区块奖励吧</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles APP（原CMT Wallet）3.0 正式上线，*手机APP权益投票CMT功能上线了*！现在用户可以使用CyberMiles APP 将CMT 权益投</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stake with CyberMiles App to get Block Award</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles App (formerly CMT Wallet) 3.0 enables staking function today!!! Hooray! Now CMT holders can get block award by staking with mobile App!
After the mainnet upgrade, the main factors for block award calculation are:
 Total staked amount in the whole CyberMiles network.
 The validator’s compensation rate. The lower the remuneration rate, the better for the staker (delegator).
 Your staked CMT amount. the higher the amount, the higher the block award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如何使用CyberMiles APP 进行权益投票，获取区块奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles APP（原CMT Wallet）已经开通权益投票功能，现在CMT 持有者可以通过手机APP获得区块奖励收入啦！ 经过主链升级后，现在区块奖励的主</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay：一种新型DApp</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190621-fairplay-dapp-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190621-fairplay-dapp-zh/</guid>
      <description>什么是FairPlay FairPlay 使用智能合约进行公平透明的自动抽奖。 它允许任何人创建并参与抽奖等电商营销活动。 根据Google Analystics，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay: a new type of DApp</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190620-fairplay-dapp-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190620-fairplay-dapp-en/</guid>
      <description>Credits: FairPlay is developed by Second State, an open source enterprise smart contract platform, and deployed on the CyberMiles public blockchain.
What is FairPlay FairPlay uses smart contracts to conduct automated prize draws that are fair and transparent. It allows anyone to create and participate in product giveaways and e-commerce marketing campaigns. Since its launch, FairPlay has routinely reached a DAU (Daily Active Users) of 1000 (according to Google Analytics), with each giveaway receiving hundreds of on-chain transactions, making it one of the most popular DApps of all public blockchains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles 公链新上线超级节点SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles 公链新上线了超级节点SNZ Holding。SNZ Holding 将自我权益投票300万CMT，报酬比率为25%。 SNZ Holding致力于提供专业的POS矿</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today CyberMiles Blockchain Welcomes Another Validator, SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles community embraces a newcomer Validator today! SNZ Holding, CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; newest Validator, is up and running, joining in the maintainance of the network security of CyberMiles blockchain.
To be a Validator, SNZ Holding has self-staked 3 million CMTs as a commitment to CMT Community. It claims a compensation rate of 25% for all its delegators.
SNZ Holding is an institution dedicated to providing high-standard and professional POS validation services. SNZ has been engaged in investment, consultancy, community building and other business related to blockchain since 2016 and is an early investor in Ethereum, Dfinity, Cosmos, Polkadot and other renowned projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a shiny lipstick from HashQuark ($37 USD value)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190617-giveaway10-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190617-giveaway10-en/</guid>
      <description>Ready for the last prize with @FairPlayDapp launch campaign?
FairPlay Dapp is the world’s most transparent lucky draw tool for you to draw a prize! Fair, automated, and decentralized prize drawings. Powered by and guaranteed by blockchain smart contracts! No shenanigans. Try your luck today. The winners are chosen by smart contracts with its embedded random number generator. See how it works.
Today’s the very last and special prize is from HashQuark!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles公链双周报(0614更新)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-biweeklyreport-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-biweeklyreport-zh/</guid>
      <description>大家好, 为您带来CyberMiles 公链在2019.05.25-2019.06.14期间的进展。 Ps: 上周因为端午小长假，推迟一周更新双周报 1.CMT Wallet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a Limited Edition Metal Art from AnChain.ai ($499 USD value)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-fairplay9-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-fairplay9-en/</guid>
      <description>Smart contract safety is extremely important for DApps. The winner drawing of the FairPlay smart contract is based on a safe random number generated by CyberMiles Validators. The secure random number generator for smart contracts is a key innovation of CyberMiles.
CyberMiles has a strong technology partnership with AnChain.ai, an AI-powered blockchain security firm. In 2018, AnChain.ai detected the first Blockchain APT (BAPT) hack in history: BAPT-FOMO3D that stole $4 millions worth of ETHs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a Philips Electric Shaver for Father&#39;s Day gift, sponsored by Lvl.99</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190613-giveaway8-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190613-giveaway8-en/</guid>
      <description>Father’s Day is just around the corner! Do you have a gift in mind for Dad? The man who has been the most caring guardian for you deserves something nice! No idea yet? This is where CyberMiles comes to rescue! Enter to win a Philips Electric Shaver ($50).
This prize is sponsored by lvl.99, a CyberMiles genesis Validator. Lvl 99 is based in Jakarta, Indonesia. It represents a group of Indonesia investors who had supported CyberMiles since day one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win 666 IRIS tokens x 3, sponsored by IRIS Network</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190612-giveaway7-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190612-giveaway7-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.
 The FairPlay DApp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in product promotions and giveaways. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already one of the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win 600 LiMaGo tokens for traveling guide service, sponsored by LiMaGo</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190611-giveaway6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190611-giveaway6-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles, a public blockchain for ecommerce, is doing a 2-week giveaway campaign to celebrate the grand launch of the new DApp, FairPlay.
The FairPlay Dapp, ran on CyberMiles, empowers everyone to create and take part in online raffles. You can use it to do givaways for product promotions, game among friends or anything you can think of. With inbeded search engine and ecommerce products smart contract creation function, FairPlayDapp is a key technology milestone to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a CMT Cube, sponsored by SSSnodes</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190610-giveaway5-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190610-giveaway5-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in online raffles, giveaways for product promotions etc. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already amoung the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. Read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a pass to DeveloperWeek New York each</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190607-giveaway4-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190607-giveaway4-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in online raffles, giveaways for product promotions etc. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already amoung the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. Read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win two 2,888 HPTs Prizes, sponsored by Huobi Pool</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190606-giveaway3-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190606-giveaway3-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in product promotions and giveaways. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already one of the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. You can read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a  unique Tiffany Corkscrew, sponsored by 5miles</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190605-giveaway2-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190605-giveaway2-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles proudly launched FairPlay Dapp on 4th of June, for every one to create and take part in lucky draws with a few clicks. This lucky draw Dapp is a key milesstone to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized marketplace.
Meanwhile, a grandiose 10-days campaign ran on @FairPlayDap empowered with CyberMiles public blockchain was kicked off. A new lucky draw is to be announced everyday for 10 days to draw lucky winners with FairPlayDapp!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>